Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally arrived at Marineford
to rescue his brother Ace.
Aided by new friends and old enemies alike,
Luffy battles against the Navy.
Thanks to a final charge from Whitebeard's associates,
success is within Luffy's grasp at long last.
But then, the unthinkable happened.
Say goodbye.
Wait!
Luffy!
issippi is coming.
This Fairy is maken in此乱 algorithms.
Osuble Genesis où ilagit nous?
Merci entre les 번ères et leshors ceux qui l'ont en venous,
qui a jamais enqu activated,
deshors et leshorsacies du seul style de travail.
Leshors du ответ entre leshors et les entreprises,
de la mort тайします leshors et leshors.
D contratboard à nouveau entrez leshors deshors
Looking for the answer, Firefist Ace dies on the battlefield.
Firefist Ace dies on the battlefield.
Oh no!
Ace...
It can't be.
Ace, no!
Akai, you know?
Take revenge!
Kill him!
That looks bad.
Hurry up!
Get these damn things off me!
I'm trying my best, but they're just too strong.
Hey, wait a sec. He can help us.
Who's he?
You know, that guy with the weird hair that opened Ace's cuffs.
I'll make a key!
Get those cuffs off him!
And hurry!
Yeah, you're right.
Great. I don't know where he's at, but try to find him.
On it!
Now fire!
This just keeps getting worse. What's next?
You fight our brother, you fight us!
Let that be your lesson, Akainu!
It's no use. We can't stop him.
It would seem you're still alive if only barely.
I'll have to rectify that.
Don't do it!
Ace!
My, my.
You're getting forgetful in your old age.
I'm still here.
And you're not moving an inch, Grandpa.
We'll see!
Ichi-Bey!
I won't let you lay a finger on him!
You're only delaying the inevitable, you fool.
No one can stand up to me.
You were a warlord. You know what I'm capable of.
No matter the cost.
If I can delay you for even a moment, then I'll be satisfied.
I'm not afraid to die!
Jinbei!
Marco, we got the key guy!
I thought I was dead, but you saved me!
Save it for later! Unlock these cuffs!
Wait! Vice Admiral, what?
What are you...
Garb!
You stay out of this, you old fool.
That's right, Sengoku.
You better keep holding me like that.
Because if you don't, I swear that I am gonna murder Sakazuki.
Damn it all!
I need to execute a traitor, too. Seems my job is never done.
Jinbei, get down!
Haki users, what a pain.
But you're far too late.
We're so close.
Don't give up yet!
There's still a chance!
The battle has ended. Firefist is done for.
See for yourself.
Huh?
I-Ice!
Hey!
Come on!
You're okay, right?
Right?
Kate!
Don't worry, Ace. I'll get you some help, Kate.
Sorry, Luffy. I tried.
Come on!
You did great.
Thank you for trying so hard for me.
But looks like this is as far as I can go.
Forgive me.
What are you talking about?
This isn't over yet!
Somebody please! Please help him!
Hurry up!
Come on! We can still save him!
Dammit! Don't you stand there! He's dying!
This way, Doctor! Quick! It's not looking good!
Okay.
Oh, Straw Boy.
Hold on, Ace! I'm here for you!
Here! I got it!
Thanks! Move! Let me see the wound!
Please!
I'm sorry.
Sorry? What do you mean, sorry? You are a doctor, aren't you?
It's too late.
There's gotta be something.
But he's still alive!
You're not even gonna try?!
We didn't come all this way to lose him now!
You can't just give up!
It's no use.
He burned through my organs, too.
This is it for me.
I can feel it.
I can feel my life slipping away.
Don't say that!
Wait, I know! Eva!
It's not too late!
Your power! Come use it on Ace!
Please!
It helped me! It might help him, too!
Just try it, please!
We don't have much time!
Eva, I'm begging you!
Why aren't you saying anything?
Why is everyone just staying?!
Straw Boy, no!
We can't help him.
Okay?
No!
But you promised me when we were kids!
You said you'd protect your little brother, remember?
You promised me you wouldn't die!
Ace!
You so much...
You and me!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
That is the time we were getting ready.
It's time to do something so you can win!
It's not yours!
No, sir!
That was awesome.
It's OK!
It's me, we will die instead!
Look at you!
Ace, the fight's not over yet.
Please, we can still save you.
Don't tell me you're gonna give up now.
Not you.
That's not the big brother I know.
You remember your promise, don't you?
Say something.
Maybe I should have never been born.
Maybe I never deserved to live in the first place.
Huh?
If Gold Roger had a son?
What are you talking about?
It's obvious, isn't it?
He'd end up just like his dad.
Off with his damn head.
Nah.
After all the crap he started, Roger got off too easy, if you ask me.
I say we'd count up all the man's crimes and prick his boy with a needle for everyone.
Come on.
I bet all the pirates would worship that kid like a god.
We'd have to do something really nasty.
Like burn him alive and make everybody watch.
There you go.
Come on, pirates.
Why don't you go join him?
Then he'd probably cry and shut him down for good.
I'm trash just like my dad.
I should die.
Now I almost wish he didn't have a son.
I never asked to be born.
But they hated me anyway.
I can't believe you, Ace.
Didn't I just tell you to stop this?
I don't care what they said.
You're just making life harder for both of us.
Hey, are you listening to me?
Don't hurt people.
You gonna stop me, Dadon?
What?
I would have killed them all if I could.
And one of these days, I'll be strong enough.
I hardly had a will to live at all back then.
Or I wouldn't have, at least.
If it weren't for Sapo.
A certain little brother I had to look after.
Didn't want you turning out like me, you know.
Oh, yeah.
If you see Dadon, tell her I said hello.
And thank her for putting up with us, too.
I never thought I'd miss a woman like her.
But I guess dying does funny things to you.
Don't say that!
You're not dying!
There is one thing that hurts.
I won't be around to see you fulfill your dream.
That's fine.
I have faith you can do it.
Because you're my brother.
Do you remember that day?
Luffy, listen.
There's only one way to live life.
And that's without any regrets.
Yeah.
Someday, we're going to head out to sea.
And live the way we want to live.
More free than anyone else.
I did it.
I lived with no regrets.
Even though it ended this way.
Can't complain.
Well, I can!
You can't die like this!
Sure.
Things could have gone better.
But it's alright.
I realized I didn't need fame or fortune after all.
All I needed was the answer to a single question.
At the very end, did I deserve to be born?
I will call you my son, who we've got plenty to talk about.
Like you not killing my son.
Ace, you're my brother!
Damn it!
Say whatever mean stuff you want!
I'm still going to save you!
Listen up, pirates!
Bring Ace to safety!
And once you're done with that, destroy the Navy!
Shut off!
You're not going to kill Ace!
Finally!
I told you I'd do it!
I'm here!
But tell me one last thing.
Are you happy to have this old fool as your father?
I can't raise my voice anymore.
Too weak.
Could you tell everyone else what I'm about to say when I'm done?
Pops, my family, and you, Luffy, thank you for caring about someone like me, who's good
for nothing, who this world never wanted, who has such bad blood in his veins.
Thank you...
for loving me...
I...
Old man, yeah, tell me the truth.
Did I deserve to be born or was it just a mistake?
That's not for me to say.
You just keep living and hope you find out.
Ace...
Ace, no.
Witnessing the death of his brother right before his eyes, Luffy falls into a state of shock, unable to move or speak.
Yet, the battle rages on around him.
Unleashing the full extent of his fury, Whitebeard threatens to bring the walls of Marineford crashing down.
On the next One Piece, the Navy Headquarters falls, Whitebeard's unspeakable wrath, I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Ace, no.
Ace.